

#### GANGARIG NYAMSUREN

#### • DETAILS •

Wien Austria +436603911915 gangarign@gmail.com

#### LINKS

Linkedin

Portfolio

#### SKILLS

PHP

React

Node.js

MySQL SQL

Git

HTML & CSS

JavaScript

Angular

Bootstrap

GitHub

**AJAX** 

API

Typescript

SCRUM

Kanban

Symfony

#### LANGUAGES

English

German

Mongolian

#### PROFILE

2/2

I am an aspiring developer who is currently gathering experience, particularly in the field of web development.

I had the opportunity to work in a tech store where I built custom computers to meet the specific needs of customers. During that time, I also studied computer science at the National University of Mongolia for two years. This experience introduced me to computer science and allowed me to hone my coding skills to a higher level.

Throughout my work experience, I have developed strong customer service skills, the ability to work effectively in a team, and the ability to continuously learn and improve my skills. Currently, I am excited to be preparing for Tech Forest and am eager to continue growing as a developer.

#### EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Customer Service at Best Western Tuushin Hotel, Ulaanbaatar, Mongolia

January 2015 — September 2015

PC Assembly Technician at Itzone.mn & itstore.mn, Ulaanbaatar, Mongolia

February 2013 — January 2015

Service staff at Restaurantsbetriebs GmbH, Wien

March 2018 — 2023

#### EDUCATION

Erdenet complex school, Erdenet

June 2012

High school graduation

Information Technology, National University of Mongolia, Ulaanbaatar

2013 - 2015

2 years of studies in Information Technology.

Full Stack Developer, CodeFactory, Wien

September 2022 — December 2022

Graduated CodeFactory as Full-stack Developer

#### **■** REFERENCES

Eikho Jeong from Restaurantsbetriebs GmbH

eikho@akakiko.at · +436644368889

#### Christoph Pirringer from CodeFactory GmbH

christoph.pirringer@codefactory.wien · +43699 12255185

# CERTICATE No:766



## Gangaria Nyannsuren

is hereby awarded the certification of

### Full Stack Web Developer

The holder of this certification has proven skills in web development technologies of both Frontend and Backend applications. These qualifications include, but are not limited to, HTML 5, CSS 3, JavaScript, Bootstrap, Typescript, Angular, PHP, Symfony, AJAX, API, and MySQL. Complementary, the holder has demonstrated proficiency in areas such as SCRUM and Kanban to help in Project Management, in testing tool areas such as PHP Unit Testing and Jasmine as well as participated continuously in Teamwork tasks.

Issued on: 15 December 2022

Christoph Pirringer

Head of education



OLOLIO de Factory CEO